const { 
    v1: uuidv1,
    v4: uuidv4,
  } = require('uuid');

const categories = [
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test0?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test2?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test3?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test4?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test5?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
    {
        question_id: uuidv4(),
        question: "is this a test6?",
        answer: "yesn",
        category: "TESTINGn",
        points: 1000,
        difficulty: 10,                     
    },
];


const questions = [
    {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "The Urawa Reds plays this sport",
          answer: "Soccer",
          category: "sports",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
    {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is a Japanese sport. You use bamboo swords to hit your opponent.",
          answer: "Kendo",
          category: "sports",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This sport is played in a pool.",
          answer: "Swimming",
          category: "sports",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This sport is played by firing arrows at a target.",
          answer: "Archery",
          category: "sports",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This sport is played by hitting a small ball into a hole.",
          answer: "Golf",
          category: "sports",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is what the teachers write on in the classroom.",
          answer: "Blackboard",
          category: "at school",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This room has many books. You can go there to study.",
          answer: "Library",
          category: "at school",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is where you go to buy food.",
          answer: "Cafeteria",
          category: "at school",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is where you go to play sports outdoors.",
          answer: "Field/Grounds",
          category: "at school",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is where you go to play sports indoors and have ceremonies. ",
          answer: "Gymnasium",
          category: "at school",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "You learn how to do calculations in this subject.",
          answer: "Math",
          category: "School Subjects",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "You learn about and play sports in this subject.",
          answer: "Physical Education",
          category: "School Subjects",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "You learn about the past in this subject.",
          answer: "History",
          category: "School Subjects",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "You learn about the human body and other living things in this subject.",
          answer: "Biology",
          category: "School Subjects",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "You learn about maps in this subject.",
          answer: "Geography",
          category: "School Subjects",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This person helps students to learn.",
          answer: "Teacher",
          category: "jobs",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This person makes food.",
          answer: "Cook/Chef",
          category: "jobs",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This person performs in movies.",
          answer: "Actor/Actress",
          category: "jobs",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This person is a doctor for animals.",
          answer: "Veterinarian",
          category: "jobs",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This person fixes cars.",
          answer: "Mechanic",
          category: "jobs",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is a fruit. It is long and yellow. It tastes sweet.",
          answer: "Banana",
          category: "food",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "The meat comes from cows.",
          answer: "Beef",
          category: "food",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is a popular food for Japanese people around Christmas time.",
          answer: "Fried Chicken/KFC",
          category: "food",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "This is a popular breakfast food. They are white or brown. You crack it to cook it.",
          answer: "Egg",
          category: "food",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "It is usually made of meat in between two buns. You can buy it at McDonald's.",
          answer: "Hamburger",
          category: "food",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      
      
      /*{
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 200,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 300,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 400,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 500,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },
      {
          question_id: uuidv4(),
          question: "",
          answer: "",
          category: "",
          points: 100,
          difficulty: 1,                     
      },*/
      
  ];

  module.exports = {categories, questions};